[	
   {
            "type": "ArithmeticPracticeState",
        "name":"SpeedTest",
		"desc_head": "SpeedTest_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "SpeedTest_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
           [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "67         ", "solution": 67} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }]
					]
	},
{
    "type": "ArithmeticPracticeFinishedState_return",
    "desc_head": "SymbolicNumberComparison_HEAD",
    "desc_body": "SymbolicNumberComparison_BODY",
    "done": false,
    "saved": false,
    "trials": [
      [ { "name": "TaskHandler", "params": { "num_left": "1", "num_right": "2", "solution": 2, "distance": 1 } }, { "name": "TotalTime" } ] ] },

	{
		"type": "ArithmeticState",
        "name":"SpeedTest",
		"desc_head": "SpeedTest_HEAD",
		"desc_body": "SpeedTest_BODY",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"trials": [
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "7         ", "solution": 7} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "6         ", "solution": 6} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "3         ", "solution": 3} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "1         ", "solution": 1} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "5         ", "solution": 5} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "8         ", "solution": 8} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "4         ", "solution": 4} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "0         ", "solution": 0} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "2         ", "solution": 2} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "9         ", "solution": 9} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "45         ", "solution": 45} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17         ", "solution": 17} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "58         ", "solution": 58} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "53         ", "solution": 53} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74         ", "solution": 74} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24         ", "solution": 24} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91         ", "solution": 91} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "48         ", "solution": 48} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "26         ", "solution": 26} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20         ", "solution": 20} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "75         ", "solution": 75} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19         ", "solution": 19} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "36         ", "solution": 36} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74         ", "solution": 74} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "44         ", "solution": 44} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "29         ", "solution": 29} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "37         ", "solution": 37} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "33         ", "solution": 33} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92         ", "solution": 92} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22         ", "solution": 22} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "61         ", "solution": 61} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76         ", "solution": 76} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "52         ", "solution": 52} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "31         ", "solution": 31} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "45         ", "solution": 45} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "44         ", "solution": 44} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "29         ", "solution": 29} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97         ", "solution": 97} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "58         ", "solution": 58} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11         ", "solution": 11} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10         ", "solution": 10} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "52         ", "solution": 52} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "96         ", "solution": 96} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92         ", "solution": 92} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "93         ", "solution": 93} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "50         ", "solution": 50} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "57         ", "solution": 57} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97         ", "solution": 97} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13         ", "solution": 13} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19         ", "solution": 19} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "57         ", "solution": 57} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "86         ", "solution": 86} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46         ", "solution": 46} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "21         ", "solution": 21} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "95         ", "solution": 95} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14         ", "solution": 14} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23         ", "solution": 23} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19         ", "solution": 19} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "90         ", "solution": 90} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "42         ", "solution": 42} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "36         ", "solution": 36} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "38         ", "solution": 38} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15         ", "solution": 15} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "16         ", "solution": 16} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "47         ", "solution": 47} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97         ", "solution": 97} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "66         ", "solution": 66} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "79         ", "solution": 79} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12         ", "solution": 12} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "41         ", "solution": 41} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "52         ", "solution": 52} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "26         ", "solution": 26} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "70         ", "solution": 70} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51         ", "solution": 51} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51         ", "solution": 51} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "89         ", "solution": 89} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "79         ", "solution": 79} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "45         ", "solution": 45} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "70         ", "solution": 70} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85         ", "solution": 85} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22         ", "solution": 22} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94         ", "solution": 94} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19         ", "solution": 19} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "66         ", "solution": 66} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68         ", "solution": 68} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "33         ", "solution": 33} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "75         ", "solution": 75} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76         ", "solution": 76} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "69         ", "solution": 69} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "60         ", "solution": 60} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17         ", "solution": 17} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20         ", "solution": 20} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68         ", "solution": 68} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85         ", "solution": 85} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24         ", "solution": 24} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11         ", "solution": 11} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "31         ", "solution": 31} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "44         ", "solution": 44} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "95         ", "solution": 95} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46         ", "solution": 46} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "59         ", "solution": 59} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "87         ", "solution": 87} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "56         ", "solution": 56} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "97         ", "solution": 97} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "92         ", "solution": 92} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94         ", "solution": 94} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "35         ", "solution": 35} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24         ", "solution": 24} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "89         ", "solution": 89} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "32         ", "solution": 32} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "18         ", "solution": 18} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "71         ", "solution": 71} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "38         ", "solution": 38} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "80         ", "solution": 80} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "32         ", "solution": 32} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "62         ", "solution": 62} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "32         ", "solution": 32} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "37         ", "solution": 37} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "52         ", "solution": 52} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22         ", "solution": 22} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85         ", "solution": 85} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "58         ", "solution": 58} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74         ", "solution": 74} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73         ", "solution": 73} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94         ", "solution": 94} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "57         ", "solution": 57} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "66         ", "solution": 66} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "28         ", "solution": 28} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14         ", "solution": 14} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "73         ", "solution": 73} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "36         ", "solution": 36} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51         ", "solution": 51} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "74         ", "solution": 74} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "43         ", "solution": 43} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81         ", "solution": 81} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "65         ", "solution": 65} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "58         ", "solution": 58} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "52         ", "solution": 52} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "35         ", "solution": 35} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "48         ", "solution": 48} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46         ", "solution": 46} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "47         ", "solution": 47} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91         ", "solution": 91} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12         ", "solution": 12} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "60         ", "solution": 60} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "54         ", "solution": 54} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "21         ", "solution": 21} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23         ", "solution": 23} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10         ", "solution": 10} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "47         ", "solution": 47} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "48         ", "solution": 48} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "25         ", "solution": 25} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "85         ", "solution": 85} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "23         ", "solution": 23} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "76         ", "solution": 76} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "13         ", "solution": 13} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "19         ", "solution": 19} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "68         ", "solution": 68} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "41         ", "solution": 41} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "78         ", "solution": 78} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "10         ", "solution": 10} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "53         ", "solution": 53} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "56         ", "solution": 56} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "88         ", "solution": 88} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46         ", "solution": 46} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "12         ", "solution": 12} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "79         ", "solution": 79} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "77         ", "solution": 77} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "53         ", "solution": 53} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "24         ", "solution": 24} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "90         ", "solution": 90} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "54         ", "solution": 54} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "90         ", "solution": 90} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "69         ", "solution": 69} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "31         ", "solution": 31} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "51         ", "solution": 51} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "35         ", "solution": 35} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11         ", "solution": 11} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "14         ", "solution": 14} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "49         ", "solution": 49} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "69         ", "solution": 69} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "87         ", "solution": 87} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "94         ", "solution": 94} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "54         ", "solution": 54} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "91         ", "solution": 91} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "90         ", "solution": 90} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20         ", "solution": 20} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "79         ", "solution": 79} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "93         ", "solution": 93} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "30         ", "solution": 30} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "49         ", "solution": 49} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "48         ", "solution": 48} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "34         ", "solution": 34} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "70         ", "solution": 70} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "64         ", "solution": 64} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "42         ", "solution": 42} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "99         ", "solution": 99} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "95         ", "solution": 95} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11         ", "solution": 11} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84         ", "solution": 84} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "17         ", "solution": 17} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "43         ", "solution": 43} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "62         ", "solution": 62} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81         ", "solution": 81} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "22         ", "solution": 22} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "48         ", "solution": 48} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "72         ", "solution": 72} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15         ", "solution": 15} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "40         ", "solution": 40} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "66         ", "solution": 66} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "33         ", "solution": 33} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "46         ", "solution": 46} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "59         ", "solution": 59} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "11         ", "solution": 11} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "55         ", "solution": 55} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "54         ", "solution": 54} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84         ", "solution": 84} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "47         ", "solution": 47} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "39         ", "solution": 39} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "61         ", "solution": 61} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "36         ", "solution": 36} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "32         ", "solution": 32} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "66         ", "solution": 66} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "25         ", "solution": 25} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "29         ", "solution": 29} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83         ", "solution": 83} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "86         ", "solution": 86} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "15         ", "solution": 15} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "96         ", "solution": 96} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "84         ", "solution": 84} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "83         ", "solution": 83} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "20         ", "solution": 20} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "81         ", "solution": 81} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "103         ", "solution": 103} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "163         ", "solution": 163} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "181         ", "solution": 181} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "180         ", "solution": 180} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "143         ", "solution": 143} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "292         ", "solution": 292} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "153         ", "solution": 153} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "204         ", "solution": 204} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "167         ", "solution": 167} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "123         ", "solution": 123} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "108         ", "solution": 108} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "284         ", "solution": 284} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "145         ", "solution": 145} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "286         ", "solution": 286} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "204         ", "solution": 204} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "122         ", "solution": 122} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "282         ", "solution": 282} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "297         ", "solution": 297} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "272         ", "solution": 272} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "245         ", "solution": 245} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "264         ", "solution": 264} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "135         ", "solution": 135} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "153         ", "solution": 153} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "224         ", "solution": 224} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "280         ", "solution": 280} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "273         ", "solution": 273} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "181         ", "solution": 181} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "140         ", "solution": 140} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "281         ", "solution": 281} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "155         ", "solution": 155} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "114         ", "solution": 114} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "295         ", "solution": 295} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "253         ", "solution": 253} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "288         ", "solution": 288} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "159         ", "solution": 159} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "202         ", "solution": 202} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "173         ", "solution": 173} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "218         ", "solution": 218} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "196         ", "solution": 196} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "253         ", "solution": 253} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "145         ", "solution": 145} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "123         ", "solution": 123} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "275         ", "solution": 275} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "219         ", "solution": 219} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "248         ", "solution": 248} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "124         ", "solution": 124} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "114         ", "solution": 114} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "225         ", "solution": 225} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "253         ", "solution": 253} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "153         ", "solution": 153} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "264         ", "solution": 264} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "254         ", "solution": 254} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "147         ", "solution": 147} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "225         ", "solution": 225} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }],
      [{ "name": "ArithmeticHandler", "params": { "problem": "197         ", "solution": 197} }, { "name": "TotalTime" }]

	
					]
	},

    { "name": "TaskDoneState", "type": "TaskDoneState", "desc_head": "ArithmeticState_HEAD", "desc_body": "ArithmeticState_BODY", "done": false, "saved": false, "trials": [ ] }, 
    {
		"type": "SAVE",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false
	},
	{
		"type": "REDIRECT",
		"done": false,
		"saved": false,
		"to": {
			"type": "GotoNextState"
		}
	}
]